Guide to the Trent Harris independent film collection 1977-2007
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Trent Harris independent film collection
1977-2007
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 801-581-8864 http://www.lib.utah.edu/collections/multimedia-archives/
A0832
Harris, Trent
Approximately 4 35mm films, 86 16mm films, 1 8mm film, 17 U-matic videocassettes, 12 Betacam videocassettes, 38 VHS videocassettes, 6 DVCPro videocassettes, 258 Mini DV videocassettes, 2 Hi-8 videocassettes, 3 DVDs, 1 Blu-ray disc, and 2 compact discs.
The Trent Harris independent film collection (1997-2007) consists of production elements and completed films by prominent Utah independent filmmaker Trent Harris. Materials include feature narrative films, docuemntaries, experimental films, and newsmagazine programs. The collection also contains numerous works by filmmaker C. Larry Roberts (1945-1988), a friend and colleague of Harris. This collection is part of the Utah Independent Film Archive (UIFA).
Biographical Note
Trent Harris is an independent filmmaker based in Salt Lake City, Utah. He earned Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) and Master of Fine Arts (M.F.A.) degrees from the University of Utah in the early days of its film program. After producing features for the local television newsmagazine progam EXTRA at KUTV from 1978-1981, Harris left Utah to study directing at the American Film Institue, where he produced "The Orkly Kid" (1985), based on footage he had shot for an unaired episode of EXTRA. These two films became the basis of one of Harris' best know works, The Beaver Trilogy (2000).
In addition to high profile feature films such as Rubin and Ed (1992) and Plan 10 from Outer Space, Harris had written, directed and produced numerous documentary and narrative films which have screened and won awards at film festivals around the world.
The Trent Harris independent film collection (1997-2007) consists of production elements and completed films by prominent Utah independent filmmaker Trent Harris. Materials include feature narrative films, docuemntaries, experimental films, and newsmagazine programs. In addition to recognizeable titles such as Rubin and Ed, Plan 10 from Outer Space, The Beaver Trilogy, and Delightful Water Universe, this collection includes Harris' student films, early work for KUTV News, and numerous narratives and documentaries. The collection also contains numerous works by filmmaker C. Larry Roberts (1945-1988), a friend and colleague of Harris. This collection is part of the Utah Independent Film Archive (UIFA).
Materials are arranged alphabetically
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
See also the Trent Harris papers (Accn 2175) and photograph collection (P1203).
Roberts, C. Larry; Utah; Independent filmmakers; Media and Communication; Moving Images; Sound Recordings; Oral Histories; Moving images; Sound recordings
- 2. strong willed women C. Larry Roberts, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 1)
- 1. Stringless yoyo 2. Magic mouse, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 2)
- 1990's experimental movie Karl's Korn Trent Harris, U-matic videocassette (Cassette 3)
- 4 Joe Frank films, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 4)
- 9 mile canyon 2004, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 5)
- A call in the night by Joe Frank, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 6)
- Agatha Christie, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 7)
- Aki USA, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 8)
- Alley pan handling w/p and audio, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 9)
- Antelope 1 6/22/96, 1996 June 22; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 10)
- Archive D.W.U. shoottapes, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 11)
- Archive DWU shoottapes, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 12)
- Artists models, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 13)
- Artists models 1 and 2 2:47, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 14)
- Attack of the giant brine shrimp (directed by Mike Cassidy), plus 2 DVD copies, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 15)
- Australia, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 16)
- Background boy, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 17)
- Barons (master 16mm), 1977; DVD (Disc 18)
- Barons Motorcycle Gang (magstock), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 19)
- Beaver Kid, Undated; Blu-ray (Disc 20)
- Beaver Kid, Undated; DVCPro videocassette (Cassette 21)
- Beaver Kid, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 22)
- Beaver Kid 30 min, Beaver Kid 2 20 min, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 23)
- Beaver Kid Sean Penn, Undated; Betamax videocassette (Cassette 24)
- Beaver Kid Sean Penn color and 2nd Joy, greatest love story ever told, Wild goose/naked reality parts 1-2, Undated; Blu-ray (Disc 25)
- Beaver Trilogy, Undated; HDcam videocassette (Cassette 26)
- Beaver Trilogy, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 27)
- Beaver Trilogy - interview Trent Harris This American Life NPR, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 28)
- Beaver Trilogy supporting role auditions, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 29)
- Bicknell UFO fest 8/2/96, Mormon cricket 11/30/96, 1996 August 2, 1996 November 30; Audiocassette (Cassette 30)
- Biff 1 7/26/96, 1996 July 26; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 31)
- Biff #2 7/27/96, 1996 July 27; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 32)
- Biff 1999, L.A. riots, W.G. end, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 33)
- Biff 3rd, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 34)
- Bishop by John Bredar, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 35)
- Bits and pieces, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 36)
- Bokou - New York City 8/1992, 1992 August; Audiocassette (Cassette 37)
- Bokov (NYC street artist), Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 38)
- Brail master Brazil 6, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 39)
- Brazil, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 40)
- Burma 2006 tapes 1-5, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 41)
- Burma 2006, free Burma rangers war footage, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 42)
- Burning man, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 43)
- Burning man, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 44)
- Burning man 8:05 (might be Rubin and Ed instead?), Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 45)
- Bushisms master 5:30 min, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 46)
- C Larry Roberts films - Eureka! Search of Virgins, My home town, Land opus dance film, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 47)
- Cambodia, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 48)
- Cambodia 2005 - temple looting, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 49)
- Cambodia Neeson, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 50)
- Ceasar's park Sarah Price 65:00, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 51)
- Charles Manson 1982, Audiocassette (Cassette 52)
- Charles Manson 1985 (music), Audiocassette (Cassette 53)
- Charles Manson channel 2 news 5/1/87, 1987 May 1; VHS videocassette (Cassette 54)
- Charles Manson interview (NBC tomorrow show 2/9/87), 1987 February 9; VHS videocassette (Cassette 55)
- Charles Manson news coverage 4/29/87, 4/30/87 channel 2, 1987 April 29, 1987 April 30; VHS videocassette (Cassette 56)
- Chief Rolling Thunder and his house, 1978 May; 16mm film (Reel 57)
- Chief Rolling Thunder of the Mountains, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 58)
- Chief Rolling Thunder of the Mountains (magstock), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 59)
- Chuck Bowden at Ken Sander 7/10/05, 2005 July 10; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 60)
- City 1 Salt Lake City cover, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 61)
- City 2 Salt Lake City cover, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 62)
- City 3, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 63)
- Cleanflix 7/2005, 2005 July; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 64)
- Conrad Brooks in Conrad Brooks vs. werewolf, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 65)
- Contains: Artists models, Amazing folks, 1950's strange footage, Dishonest sheep painfully chastised 1, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 66)
- Couch potatoes, circus, frozen zoo, rocket, Chief Rolling Thunder of the mountains, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 67)
- Crab Louse Trent Harris, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 68)
- Craig Baldwin's Sonic outlaws 87 min, 1995; VHS videocassette (Cassette 69)
- Crispin Glover on Letterman show, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 70)
- Crispin Glover screen test, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 71)
- Cunnamulla, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 72)
- D.W.U. sassy, Makat, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 73)
- Dalton Mexico - master edit, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 74)
- Delightful water universe, Undated; Blu-ray (Disc 75)
- Delightful water universe Trent mix ng audio mix no good, Undated; DV videocassette (Cassette 76)
- Dog, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 77)
- Down in the valley a film by Morton Rosenfeld, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 78)
- Downtown, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 79)
- Dr. Who episode 2/19/95, Trent Harris interview ch. 4 Plan 10 2/19/95, 1995 February 19; VHS videocassette (Cassette 80)
- Driuin's swell mm4 4/20/97, 1997 April 20; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 81)
- Early TV and Philo T. Farnsworth on I've got a secret, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 82)
- Ed Abby - produced by Ned Judge, 1 DVD copy, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 83)
- Edit tape - Arist model 1, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 84)
- Elements of Dishonest sheep painfully chastised 2, Save more lambs, Farm family, Army enima film, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 85)
- Emmons interview with Charles Manson, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 86)
- Enema (US army medical film), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 87)
- Extra - 141 extras, ROTC, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 88)
- Extra story: State street 5/18/79, 1979 May 18; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 89)
- Extra: atomic tv, dog catcher, seagulls, soldier of fortune, Gill Huff, the church of Jayne Mansfield, foxfire, subliminal shoes, tank heads, oil-getty, space invaders, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 90)
- Extra: atomic tv, subliminal shoes, Romero (George Romero), oil-getty, soldiers of fortune, lost Vegas weddings, Allen Ginsberg, seagulls, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 91)
- Extra: subliminal shoes, soldiers of fortune, tank heads, dog catcher, oil-getty, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 92)
- Found footage: beach and bodies, Ben Franklin and kite, indian smoke signials, space shuttles and early animation, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 93)
- Freetown Sierra Leone - R.U.F. invasion 1999, VHS videocassette (Cassette 94)
- Geraldo/Manson, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 95)
- Gerard Straub L.A. 2005, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 96)
- Guns 4, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 97)
- Gyll Huff, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 98)
- Gyll's hair, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 99)
- Hansen Planetarium Planetarium spot 10:45, 1995 December 20; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 100)
- Hansen Planetarium Space, time, Utah :30, 1996 January 2; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 101)
- Hare Krisna's chanting, 1996 January 2; DVC-33 videocassette (Cassette 102)
- Hobo 1977, 16mm film (Reel 103)
- Hobo 1980s, 16mm film (Reel 104)
- Hobo orig. A and B outs, 1978; 16mm film (Reel 105)
- Hobo original A-B outs 2, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 106)
- Hobo original pan handling alley, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 107)
- Hobo roper d, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 108)
- Hobo w/p nite train nite roper, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 109)
- Hobo/Elko 1980s, 16mm film (Reel 110)
- Hobos, 1 VHS copy in addition, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 111)
- Hobos 1, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 112)
- Hobos 2, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 113)
- Hobos 3, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 114)
- Hobos 4, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 115)
- Hobos (A-roll 1), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 116)
- Hobos (A-roll 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 117)
- Hobos (B-roll 1), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 118)
- Hobos (B-roll 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 119)
- Hobos 1977 trains 2 rolls mix audio tape, 16mm film (Reel 120)
- Hobos answer prints (2), telescene (1), 3 rolls magnetic mix (3), 1977; 16mm film (Reel 121)
- Hobos misc. w/p trims, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 122)
- Hobos ride 1977, 16mm film (Reel 123)
- Hobos roper a, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 124)
- Hobos roper b, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 125)
- Hobos roper c, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 126)
- Hobos roper e, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 127)
- Hobos w/p and mix, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 128)
- Home movies 1, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 129)
- Home movies 1 - Trent's family 1950's, VHS videocassette (Cassette 130)
- Home movies 2, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 131)
- Hong Kong churches December 2004, 2004 December; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 132)
- Howard Finster, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 133)
- Howard Finster 2, paradise garden, grandson Andy talks about TV, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 134)
- Howard Finster man of visions, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 135)
- Iceland by Joe Frank 1991 subscription drive KCRW tape 1, VHS videocassette (Cassette 136)
- Iceland by Joe Frank 1991 subscription drive KCRW tape 2, VHS videocassette (Cassette 137)
- Iceland by Joe Frank 1991 subscription drive KCRW tape 3, VHS videocassette (Cassette 138)
- IJM video for PBS Nov. 2009, 2009 November; CD (Disc 139)
- Indo 2001, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 140)
- Iraq footage, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 141)
- Job 2 broken, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 142)
- Joe Frank Decline of spangler, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 143)
- Joe Frank: work in progress A tour of the city 1, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 144)
- Joe Frank: work in progress A tour of the city 3, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 145)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Arena, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 146)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Emerald Isle, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 147)
- Joe Frank: work in progress I'm not crazy, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 148)
- Joe Frank: work in progress In the dark 1, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 149)
- Joe Frank: work in progress In the dark 2, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 150)
- Joe frank: work in progress In the middle of nowhere 1, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 151)
- Joe frank: work in progress In the middle of nowhere 2, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 152)
- Joe frank: work in progress In the middle of nowhere 3, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 153)
- Joe Frank: work in progress On the edge, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 154)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Pilot, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 155)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Rent a family 1, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 156)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Rent a family 2, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 157)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Rent a family 3, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 158)
- Joe Frank: work in progress Road to hell, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 159)
- John Allison - Manson interview, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 160)
- Joyce final pic, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 161)
- Joyce graphics, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 162)
- Joyce heart and key, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 163)
- Joyce Hollywood pix, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 164)
- Joyce McKinney interview and cover 1, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 165)
- Joyce McKinney interview and cover 3, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 166)
- Joyce McKinney more pics newspaper, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 167)
- Joyce McKinney pics kirk, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 168)
- Joyce McKinney stills and stories, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 169)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told 8, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 170)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (edited magstock), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 171)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (magstock), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 172)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (magstock, truck aa), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 173)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (music, magstock), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 174)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (roll 3 magstock), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 175)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (roll 3), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 176)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (roll 4 magstock and roll 4), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 177)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (roll aa), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 178)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (work print 1 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 179)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (work print 2 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 180)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (work print with trims 1 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 181)
- Joyce McKinney: Greatest love story ever told (work print with trims 2 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 182)
- Joyce music, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 183)
- Joyce stills law, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 184)
- Judith Hallet, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 185)
- Jungle Marauders, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 186)
- Kaz the rapper, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 187)
- King of the echo people, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 188)
- KTVX - Plan 10 premiere - Sundance 1/1996, 1996 January; VHS videocassette (Cassette 189)
- KUTV - docu Hobo film net, Undated; 16mm reel (Reel 190)
- KUTV extra ch. 2 3/5/2, September 20; 16mm reel (Reel 191)
- KUTV news - Plan 10 coverage, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 192)
- L.A. Riots, Undated; DVC-33 videocassette (Cassette 193)
- Laos 2001 2004, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 194)
- Larry Roberts punk rock, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 195)
- Leisure medallions (glass factory), Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 196)
- Lonsom Beaver, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 197)
- Louisiana prison B-roll, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 198)
- Lunchroom manners, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 199)
- Magic mouse magazine program 1 sampler, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 200)
- Mali, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 201)
- Manson, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 202)
- Manson - good fromme, Undated; Audioassette (Cassette 203)
- Manson free-form, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 204)
- Manson in a Vacaville prison, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 205)
- Mark Pauline (2 copies), Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 206)
- Master - kids, world in our walls, hear our voices, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 207)
- McKinney stills, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 208)
- McKinney stills new west, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 209)
- Mdube choirs Johannesburg, South Africa 7/23/88, 1988 July 23; VHS videocassette (Cassette 210)
- Mdube interviews Durban 3/8/88, 1988 March 8; VHS videocassette (Cassette 211)
- Mdube practices Durban, South Africa 8/5/88, 1988 August 5; VHS videocassette (Cassette 212)
- Mighty mouse mother goose's birthday party, Undated; 8mm film (Reel 213)
- Misc w/p Hobos Bon interview cowboy, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 214)
- Moki mac master 4/14/1999, 1999 April 14; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 215)
- Mondoshow - Olympics, monde wonders, Bush staries, screening tape for save our canyons fundraiser, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 216)
- Mule shoe TV, Howard Finster produced by Trent Harris for NBC, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 217)
- Music from Plan 10, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 218)
- Mystery mountain acid 1, time lapse 2, factory bute, Goblin Valley, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 219)
- Mystery mt. 1 - Pet cemetery campfire, tunnel 4/20/97, trunk 4/20/97, 1997 April 20; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 220)
- Mystery mt. 2 4/20/97 tunnel good, 1997 April 20; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 221)
- Mystery mt. 3 Carlights 4/22/97 new carlights 98, Mr. Butz photos, wild goose dance, 1997 April 22; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 222)
- Mystery mt. Acid-2 Mr. Butz, oyster jar, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 223)
- Naked realilty 1, Undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 224)
- National geographic explorer Masking Indian 5/24/88, 1988 May 24; VHS videocassette (Cassette 225)
- National Geographic explorer Wild sound, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 226)
- National geographic society explorer, bio-accoustic boogie, 1989 November 3; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 227)
- Navajo Mokimac, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 228)
- Ndebele houses, Kwandebele witch doctor, market 7/24-27/88, 1988 July 24-27; VHS videocassette (Cassette 229)
- Ndebele initiation Lowa South America 7/31/88, 1988 July 31; VHS videocassette (Cassette 230)
- Ned's nuts - 1980s, U-matic videocassette (Cassette 231)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 1 KUTV, October 4 1984, film 5, 1984 October 4; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 232)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 2 KUTV, October 4 1984, film aa, 1984 October 4; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 233)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 3 KUTV, October 3 1984, films 1 and 2, 1984 October 3; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 234)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 4 KUTV, October 3 1984, film 3, 1984 October 3; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 235)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 5 KUTV, October 3 1984, film 4, 1984 October 3; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 236)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 6 KUTV, October 3 1984, film 6, 1984 October 3; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 237)
- News video film – Joyce McKinney Reel 7 KUTV, October 3 1984, film 7, 1984 October 3; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 238)
- NPR shorts, first man on moon, what is poetry, Dic Diddit 8min 48sec, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 239)
- Oaxaca 2005 cut film blessing pets, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 240)
- Oaxaca August 2005, monte alban, blessing of the pets, 2005 August; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 241)
- Ocean Psychosis (A-roll), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 242)
- Ocean Psychosis (B-roll), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 243)
- Olympics, Undated; Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 244)
- Orkly Kid, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 245)
- Orkly Kid, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 246)
- Patti in Kansas print, Undated; 16mm film (Reel 247)
- Paul Rachman, director narrative showreel written by Joe Frank, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 248)
- Perfect woman 13 min, Memories 9 min written and created by Joe Frank review from beginning, Undated; VHS videocassette (Cassette 249)
- Peru 2006 Dr. Tony Lazarra, Mini-DV videocassette (Cassette 250)
- Philo T. Farnsworth, Undated; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 251)
- Plan 10 (production master) ch1, 2 r1; ch3, 4 r2; ch5, 6 r3, Undated; Audiocassette (Cassette 252)
- Plan 10 from outer space 1 11/29/94, 1994 November 29; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 253)
- Plan 10 from outer space 2 11/29/94, 1994 November 29; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 254)
- Plan 10 from outer space 3 11/29/94, 1994 November 29; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 255)
- Plan 10 from outer space (aerial shots of SLC 1 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 256)
- Plan 10 from outer space (aerial shots of SLC 2 of 2), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 257)
- Plan 10 from outer space (foreign language), 1996; VHS videocassette (Cassette 258)
- Plan 10 from outer space (part 1 of 3), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 259)
- Plan 10 from outer space (part 2 of 3), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 260)
- Plan 10 from outer space (part 3 of 3), Undated; 16mm film (Reel 261)
- Plan 10 from outer space 1 of 2 2/22/95, 1995 February 22; U-matic videocassette (Cassette 262)
- Plan 10 from outer space 1995, VHS videocassette (Cassette 263)